Nah, this ain't my black American fight.
I'm watching outright tyranny take place in Minneapolis that is not limited by any shape
way or form.
And yet folks are fixing themselves to type letters like this.
And I don't know if this is a bot or not, but I know that there are people who absolutely
believe this.
What is your black American fight?
What does it even mean to you to be black American?
And so many of you all's black American identity is built solely on just the juxtaposition
to whiteness.
On not being white or on being able to have the access that white people have.
We got folks who have built their entire black identity on what they feel they deserve being
the descendant of slaves.
That's the crux.
So many people's black American-ness is literally just built on seeing other black Americans.
Oh, look, there's a black person in a position of power.
And then you feel like you somebody.
Your black American-ness is flimsy.
Your black American-ness is literally just built on seeing other black people, but not
actually knowing what it means to be black, not even having anything grounded in a value
system attached to blackness, a spiritual system attached to being black.
No, that's why you're so easily manipulated.
That's why it's so casual for you to call for the harm of other black folks.
That's why it takes so little effort for you to insult other black people for no reason
other than they just said something that you didn't understand or that you didn't like.
We got black folks building entire careers on denigrating other black people and calling
it gossip or calling it opinions.
No, your blackness isn't strong.
Your blackness isn't sturdy.
Your blackness isn't deep.
It's surface.
So it doesn't surprise me that you would blame your self-centered pseudo-intellectual
apolitical-ness on being black American because that's what your black American-ness is.
And there's going to be people in these comments who say, well, you don't know anything about
being black American because your mother is from Grenada.
And I would say that that has helped me even more because my father is black American and
I'm able to see the difference and understand the uniqueness of this identity and what it
is grounded in.
And I will say that we are doing a disservice to what it means to be black American.
Let me tell y'all, everything that we hold dear, it is on the precipice of complete disintegration.
So if you're going to hold on to anything, make it worthwhile and make your blackness mean
something other than just a reason to disengage.
Support a real one.